✔ a built package derives file hashes and stays valid (4.1913ms)
✔ manifest validation rejects the mistakes that would widen L3 by accident (0.6681ms)
✔ PART_KINDS stays the host-owned list (2.0011ms)
✔ compatibility gate refuses engine, base, state-format and native gaps (2.5062ms)
✔ a non-native package cannot smuggle a native library through files[] (24.533ms)
✔ license must be resolved before a part may ship (0.5271ms)
✔ content references must resolve to a hash right now (0.762ms)
✔ install refuses tampered bytes before writing anything (3.4743ms)
✔ install refuses an incompatible target without writing the package (1.0217ms)
✔ install, activate, upgrade, rollback and uninstall follow the journaled order (16.7709ms)
✔ rollback with nothing to fall back to is refused (0.9708ms)
✔ a tampered installed file blocks activation and is reported (3.8492ms)
✔ budget accounting never turns "unmeasured" into "passed" (0.4931ms)
✔ store verifies packages it wrote and can list them (3.2603ms)
✔ the L3 candidate gate blocks every documented candidate until real evidence exists (1.0289ms)
✔ a fully evidenced candidate passes, an unresolvable one does not (0.1911ms)
✔ a tampered manifest cannot hide tampered bytes: the install digest is re-checked at activation (4.0566ms)
✔ install cannot silently replace the bytes of the active version (5.8692ms)
✔ rollback refuses to restore a tampered or removed previous version (15.3022ms)
✔ uninstalling a version prunes it from the rollback history (20.312ms)
✔ the manager fills the host ABI when a target omits it (4.588ms)
✔ readPackageFromDirectory refuses paths that escape the package (1.2121ms)
✔ retrieval excludes incompatible and unresolvable entries with reasons (1.9465ms)
✔ retrieval refuses entries it cannot verify (0.1903ms)
✔ tool selection: baseline keeps everything, candidate filters and orders (5.5171ms)
✔ tool selection is deterministic and both arms share one input (0.1994ms)
✔ experiment refuses to run without a frozen set or an adapter (0.4663ms)
✔ a completed run keeps failures in the denominator and aggregates honestly (1.1458ms)
✔ run records are written only for completed runs (2.8614ms)
✔ comparison refuses across different task sets and small samples (1.4392ms)
✔ comparison reports improvement, regression and refusal to overclaim (1.8693ms)
✔ an adapter that throws leaves the task in the denominator and disables the rate (0.2903ms)
✔ allowUnverified is the only escape hatch and marks entries unverified (0.1367ms)
ℹ tests 33
ℹ suites 0
ℹ pass 33
ℹ fail 0
ℹ cancelled 0
ℹ skipped 0
ℹ todo 0
ℹ duration_ms 260.1347
