✔ read-only channels are forwarded unchanged to the core (1.6876ms)
✔ preview decodes the exact body and records real evidence (0.2251ms)
✔ a cached ok preview does not re-run the decoder (0.122ms)
✔ a failed preview is retried instead of staying locked (0.1581ms)
✔ a worker failure is recorded as failed, never as ok (0.1921ms)
✔ cancel records a cancelled state through a claimed slot (0.1506ms)
✔ the asset service contains no window, input or playback calls (0.1124ms)
ℹ tests 7
ℹ suites 0
ℹ pass 7
ℹ fail 0
ℹ cancelled 0
ℹ skipped 0
ℹ todo 0
ℹ duration_ms 111.3868
